The classic combo is back!
Good Burger 2 is a family, comedy film directed by Phil Traill.
Dexter Reed is down on his luck after another one of his inventions fails.
Ed welcomes Dex back to Good Burger with open arms
and gives him his old job back.
With a new crew working at Good Burger, Dex devises a plan to get back on his feet
but unfortunately puts the fate of Good Burger at risk once again.
Ed, played by Kel Mitchell.
Dexter Reed, played by Kenan Thompson.
Cecil McNevin, played by Lil Rel Howery.
Mia, played by Kamaia Fairburn.
Katt Bozwell, played by Jillian Bell.
ED2, played by Alex R. Hibbert.
Good Burger 2 is a 2023 American comedy film directed by Phil Traill, written by the writing team of Kevin
Kopelow and Heath Seifert, and produced by and starring Kenan Thompson and Kel Mitchell.
It serves as a sequel to Good Burger (1997), which was based on a
comedy sketch featured on the Nickelodeon series All That.
The story follows Dexter Reed reuniting with Ed at his old workplace Good Burger, where the
pair unveils a secret involving a successor to their old rival restaurant.
Talks of a sequel for Good Burger occurred in 2018 through the interest of both Thompson and Mitchell, three
years after the pair were reunited in a sketch on The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon in 2015.
The sequel was officially announced in March 2023.
Kopelow and Seifert, the co-creators of the original sketch and co-writers of the first film,
were hired to write the screenplay, and Traill was confirmed to be directing.
Thompson and Mitchell were also confirmed to be
returning as Dexter Reed and Ed, respectively.
The film was produced by Nickelodeon Movies and Artists for Artists, and was filmed from May to
June of that same year, mirroring the same production window as the original.
Record producer Oak Felder was hired to compose the film's score.
Good Burger 2 was released on November 22, 2023, on the streaming
service Paramount+, and received mixed reviews.
The film explores themes of fast food restaurant,
invention, loss of job, fast food, buddy comedy.
The tone is lighthearted.